linkrisk.com 2016-05-09

# Privacy - Kerboo

#### Your privacy is critically important to us. At Kerboo we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

â€”

Business Analysis Software Ltd. (“BAS”) operates several websites including Kerboo.com. It is BAS’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, BAS collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. BAS’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how BAS’s visitors use its website. From time to time, BAS may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

BAS also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. BAS only discloses logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to BAS’s websites choose to interact with BAS in ways that require BAS to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that BAS gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for Kerboo.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with BAS – by purchasing access to the link analysis tools, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, BAS collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with BAS. BAS does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

#### Aggregated Statistics

BAS may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, BAS may monitor the usage on Kerboo.com. BAS may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, BAS does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

BAS discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on BAS’s behalf or to provide services available at BAS’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organisations may be located outside of your home country; by using BAS’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. BAS will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations, as described above, BAS discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when BAS believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of BAS, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an BAS website and have supplied your email address, BAS may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with BAS and our products. We primarily use our various social media accounts to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. BAS takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorised access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. BAS uses cookies to help BAS identify and track visitors, their usage of BAS website, and their website access preferences. BAS visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using BAS’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of BAS’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Business Transfers

If BAS, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that BAS goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of BAS may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

#### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by BAS and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, BAS may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in BAS’s sole discretion. BAS encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.
